

VINNYK VITALII

CONTACTS

• Kyiv

+380675059113 / Viber or Telegram

in Vitalii Vinnyk

LANGUAGES

English

••••

Ukrainian

••••

Russian

....

Poland

••000

SKILLS

Conduct of negotiations

....

Creating of effective team

....

Fast learnability

••••

HOBBIES

Hiking

Jogging

Travelling

ABOUT ME

I have an experience with communicating and meeting all levels of customers.

I am possessing comprehensive QA technics, problem-solving skills and attention to details.

I have completed several commercial projects:

- testing of WEB-site's Comments application;
- testing three releases of Engineer Software, testing UI;
- fully testing of WEB-sites about travelling, holidays and restaurant themes.

Nowadays I am improving my Manual QA skill and learning Automation QA on JAVA OOP based.

Insistence in the achievement of high goals pushes me to deep dive into QA studying and to get new skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

06/2022 - PRESENT

QA ENGINEER

OKTEN

Responsibilities and duties:

- Test documentation creation (test plans, test cases, bug reports, check-lists);
- Test execution (usability testing, UI testing, confirmation testing, regression testing);
- · Black-box testing;
- Providing testing in the WEB, mobile and desktop application.

Additional technologies which were used by me in testing processes:

- REST API testing using Swagger and Postman;
- · Working in MySQL databases;
- Using JIRA bug tracking system;
- Azure for testing applications in different OS;
- Skill in distributed version control system GIT.

I am ready to increase my skill level in QA Automation alongside with Manual Testing. I have initial level in HTML/CSS, JAVA 00P and nowadays I cope with Selenium and Maven.

03/2008 - PRESENT

OWNER AND GENERAL DIRECTOR

TRADE BUD ALLIANCE, LLC

Building company with own storehouse and wares

My responsibilities for:

- Negotiations Building productive teams;
- Organization of working process of employees;
- Control financial stability of company and searching for material resources for increasing of annual results of company;
- Planning of monthly strategies with my team.

Key achievements;

- Attracted more than 20 key building customers from all of the country;
- Set supplies of building materials from abroad to Ukraine;
- 80% of building objects in Kiev region was provided by our materials.

EDUCATION

2000 - 2005

BUILDING ENGINEER

KIEV NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF BUILDING AND ARCHITECTURE

I have graduation of bachelor and magister